Various Artists Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Various Artists Slide Collection
1960-2000
VRC 103
Yale University Arts Library
2
4 boxes
Collection consists of slides of paintings, sculpture, and architecture by various artists, American and European, from ca. 1400-2000.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of slides of paintings, sculpture, and architecture by various artists (1,956 slides), American and European, from ca. 1400-2000.
Arrangement
The slides are arranged alphabetically be the artists' names. Each artist has a separate folder. Within the folders, the slides are accompanied by any available catalog material and documentation.
Art; Architecture; Slides; Reproductions
- Austin, Henry, 1801-1885 [191 slides] (Box 1)
- Blake, Peter, b. 1932 [12 slides] (Box 1)
- Boilly, Leopold, 1761-1845 [102 slides] (Box 1)
- Bomberg, David, 1890-1957 [34 slides] (Box 1)
- Claude Lorraine, 1604-1682 [53 slides] (Box 1)
- Davis, Alexander Jackson, 1803-1892 [24 slides] (Box 1)
- Denis, Maurice, 1870-1943 [13 slides] (Box 1)
- Doyle, Richard, 1824-1883 [24 slides] (Box 2)
- Guadi, Antoni, 1852-1926 [50 slides] (Box 2)
- Haendel, Karl, b. 1976 [12 slides] (Box 2)
- Hals, Frans, ca. 1581-1666 [76 slides] (Box 2)
- Hoare, Richard Colt, 1758-1838 [20 slides] (Box 2)
- Hundertwasser, Friedensreich, 1928-2000 [12 slides] (Box 2)
- Johns, Jasper, b. 1930 [37 slides] (Box 2)
- Johnson, Ray, 1927-1994 [23 slides] (Box 2)
- Kircher, Athanasius, 1602-1680 [29 slides] (Box 2)
- Mantegna, Andrea, ca. 1431-1506 [20 slides] (Box 2)
- Michelangelo Buonarotti, 1475-1564 [34 slides] (Box 2)
- Millet, Jean-François, 1814-1875 [146 slides] (Box 3)
- Mortimer, John Hamilton, 1740-1779 [12 slides] (Box 3)
- Murphy, Catherine, b. 1946 [20 slides] (Box 3)
- Pontormo, Jacopo, 1494-1557 [13 slides] (Box 3)
- Redgrave, Richard, 1804-1888 [13 slides] (Box 3)
- Rembrandt van Rijn, 1606-1669 [133 slides] (Box 3)
- Rogers, Richard, b. 1933 [33 slides] (Box 3)
- Romano, Giulio, ca. 1499-1546 [36 slides] (Box 3)
- Sarto, Andrea del, 1486-1530 [65 slides] (Box 3)
- Schille, Alice, 1869-1955 [20 slides] (Box 3)
- Seurat, Georges, 1859-1891 [23 slides] (Box 3)
- Stanczak, Julian, b. 1928 [58 slides] (Box 4)
- Sullivan, Louis, 1856-1924 [63 slides] (Box 4)
- Trumbull, John, 1756-1843 [203 slides] (Box 4)
- Turnbull, William, 1935-1977 [32 slides] (Box 4)
- Turner, J. M. W., 1775-1851 [15 slides] (Box 4)
- Vallotton, Felix, 1865-1925 [31 slides] (Box 4)
- Vedder, Elihu, 1836-1923 [70 slides] (Box 5)
- Wilkie, David, 1785-1841 [63 slides] (Box 5)
- Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959 [107 slides] (Box 5)
- Wright of Derby, Joseph, 1734-1797 [34 slides] (Box 5)
- Zittel, Andrea, b. 1965 [20 slides] (Box 5)